Interviewer: What do you do?
Talitha: I work in Marketing.
Interviewer: How many hours a week do you work?
Talitha: I work for thirty-seven hours a week.
Interviewer: Do you have a big family?
Joelle: No, I have a small family. One sister and parents.
Interviewer: How old is your sister?
Joelle: My sister is thirteen.
Interviewer: What time do you get up in the morning?
Sophie: Usually around half past seven.
Interviewer: What about at weekends?
Sophie: Much later. Probably half past nine, ten o’clock.
Interviewer: How often do you do sport or exercise?
Brian: I tend to do sports three or four times a week.
Interviewer: What do you do?
Brian: Gym three times and then I normally do some yoga.
Interviewer: What do you like about New York?
Tom: New York? The variety. The people. Change.
Interviewer: What don’t you like?
Tom: What don’t I like?
No, not much.